[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "But how many of these will he actually do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, we really think that he can do a lot of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "I mean what -- it's all very well to say that, but what would President Romney, day one, actually do or say to China to carry through that pledge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "The pledge, or the proposal, is to have China listed as a currency manipulator because they're not allowing their currency to float.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"], "LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Governor Romney"]}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, Governor Romney has always said, you know, the point of going into business is to make the business successful which is defined at least, in part, by the business being able to make a profit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "The actual list of things which are to his credit, which Republicans never give him any credit for, is actually quite impressive if you highlight those pluses, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "NNPS", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, he's been saying those things already.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "How would he get something out for this election and makes a series of further promises about what he will do in a second term, why should we believe him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, we should believe him because of the things that he's done in the first term.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "But what about the things that he promised to do that he then didn't do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, Piers, that's why we have elections and often you get a second term.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Which one do you prefer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Lingerie model.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "What do you think of the battle that we're now about to face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "It's much closer than I expected it to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Why is it -- why is it closer, do you think, than people expected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I love that I'm the authority of this because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Why shouldn't you be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, no, no, people come to me for their political insights.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "I think the Republican race was just beyond comedic joy from start to finish, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I remember tweeting during one of the debates.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "It was, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "It was very great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$10,000"]}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "$", "CD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Would you see that as a huge lottery to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I -- Piers, I have spent over $10,000 on tickets so far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Do you buy into Mitt Romney's argument that he is a proven track record businessman and therefore he can run America like a successful company?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "I mean I think -- I think he is a businessman.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "What do you, as a smart woman in America, what do you want?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Well, first of all, I would like my vagina to be taken off the table in the politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Is it on the table?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, it's been on the table.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "It could play both ways, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "It could play both ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "The statement to George, to the nation, what were you doing in those pictures?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "It's so adorable you think I was making a statement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Do you wake up in the morning and the first thing you do is head for BlackBerries, get the political news, start going at it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Yes, that's what we do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Never?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "He's been talking about it all day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "In bed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, we're both reading.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "What do you read?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Well, I'm reading the history of Islam and he's reading \"In Style\" magazine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "You talk about attachment parenting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I'm fascinated by attachment parenting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What did you make of that cover, that extraordinary cover?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "First of all, it was an extraordinary cover because the boy was, if I'm not mistaken, in camouflage pants.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Is the glory coming your way in any way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Yes, anything in it for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "ENTWORTH: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "He doesn't wake up, get the reigns (ph) and start beating his chest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No, he doesn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Doing his Tarzan impression?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "I beat my chest for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 410, "question": "But what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Well, I mean --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "What do you want for your kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Well, I'm going to home-school them now after this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "How excited are you about London?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "You know, I'm very excited.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "-- hundredth of a second, you just give up?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "No, I never give up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "You really broke your thumb hitting a wall?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I broke my thumb in the next race, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Because you were so full of rage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I was just -- I can't -- I couldn't believe that I lost by a touch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "How hard are you hitting that wall to break your thumb?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I didn't know I did it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Is there any experience in the world better than winning a gold medal at the Olympics, that you've enjoyed yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Having my daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Which one are you going to take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "I've got your mind racing back to some -- I don't know, where are we going, a beach?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Yes, something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I'm going to have to shut my mouth more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "See, I always quaintly assumed that when you get to that stage of the preparation, it's like boxers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Anyone on the American Olympic squad that you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "There are like --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "You might be the lucky recipient of my joy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I'm as old as their mothers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Are we going to stand side by side and do it together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "No, we're not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "How do you keep that six-pack looking like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Well, people have to remember I do this for a living.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "For how long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Probably between four and six hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Where do you get your information from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "I've just done a very thorough research job on you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "So did you fire him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "No, I -- he's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "What has he said about London?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "I don't like to share because I don't want to jinx anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "It'll stay between us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "And hundreds of millions of people around the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "What has he got right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "He's gotten a lot right about my personal life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "Well, I -- well, OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "He predicted you would have a daughter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Who do you talk to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Well, what you do is you go in there and he leaves the room, and you take a card, and you write down three questions that you want answered, and you write down three people that have passed away, and you sign and print your name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Which relatives, if you don't mind me asking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "My dad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Who've passed away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Yes, my dad, who passed away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "And you have, what, a conversation through this -- ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "I don't have a conversation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "Or is the first love really in that water, winning, until that's done in your life, do you think you've got a chance of -- ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Well, I guess I'll find out in a few months.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "VB", "RBR", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "I mean, do you feel that you're -- ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "I feel like when I'm ready to move on, like my dad said, is be more family oriented and settle down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "The one last gold in London?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "I actually would just like to make the Olympic team.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "You will, won't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "Susan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "What do you think they'll be feeling tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "Well, I've said over and over again that over 30 years, 33 years, they've just gone from one breaking case event to another breaking case event to another.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "Do you think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "I think that they have certainly gone very far down a road of being able to know how to track children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Have you had a favorite guest over the years besides me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 842, "question": "You don't think he's going to do the news for the rest of his life, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 843, "answer": "No, but -- and he can have my job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]